koolred.com 2012-11-18

# Koolred - Connect, Meet and Discover

## About this Privacy Policy

Customers, visitors, users, members, and others who use [Koolred.com](http://koolred.com/) or other Koolred Services (collectively or individual "Users") are governed by this Privacy Policy.

Any video, image or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the Koolred Services become published content and is not considered personally identifiable information protected under this Privacy Policy.

All defined terms in this Privacy Policy shall have the meanings ascribed to them in the Koored Terms of Use.

By using or accessing Koolred, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## Information Collection (Information We Collect)

We collect information submitted by you such as your name, email address, age and country for authentication and to send notifications relating to Koolred Services to you.

We also collect other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, school and company you work for in order to assist you in finding and communicating with each other.

In some cases where your privacy settings permit it

, other Koolred Users may be able to supplement your profile with your personal information.

Certain personally identifiable information such as your name and email address are also collected when you choose to participate in various activities on the site such as posting messages, uploading photos or videos, writing reviews, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists.

Our servers automatically record certain information (such as web request, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type.

We may employ any other techniques that are used to track your online usage patterns anonymously (i.e. in a non-personally identifiable manner) on the Website or in our emails sent to you.

You post information (as defined in the Koolred Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk.

Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.

We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that information you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorised persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site.

You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of information may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your information.

Users can choose to sign in to Koolred by using their Twitter or Facebook accounts. By virtue of choosing to exercise this option, user also permits and allows Koolred to access certain personally identifiable information of the user from these respective sites. This information includes, but is not limited to, their name, email address, gender, date of birth and country for authentification and to send notifications related to Koolred Services. Therefore, do not choose this option if it is not the user's intention to allow such information to be accessed by Koolred.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Koolred is a violation of the Koolred Terms of Service and should be reported to [askus@koolred.com](mailto:askus@koolred.com).

**Children Under Age 13** You must be 13 years of age or older to be a member. Koolred does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for Koolred or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Koolred. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will require the member to provide evidence confirming the age. If the member fails to provide such information within 48 hours of our request, we will delete all information pertaining to the member and terminate the membership immediately. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [askus@koolred.com](mailto:askus@koolred.com).

**Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18** We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

## Information Use (How We Use the Personal Information We Collect)

Your Profile information including your profile picture, first name or display name and location are displayed in order to facilitate user interaction in Koolred. 

Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join Koolred, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, your email address is not shared or displayed to people within your personal network. You communicate with members within your network through the Koolred message service, without disclosing your email address. 

Your full name is never directly revealed to other members. 

To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, Koolred allows you to search for your friends using first and last name, email address, and/or companies where you may have worked.

Data collected through cookies and 'clear GIFs' may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to you.

User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

We use your personal information to operate, maintain and provide to you the features and functionality of the Koolred Services.

Koolred may use your email address to send updates, newsletters or news regarding the service that will benefit you. You may choose not to receive email of this type by changing your "notification" settings to "Do not send me notification emails" in the user "Account Settings".

We may use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc) to improve the quality and design of the Koolred Services and to create new features, promotions, functionality and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preference and trends.

When you use Koolred, you may form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, form groups, set up events, and transmit information through various channels.

We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features.  
In most cases, we retain it so that for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friends list.

From time to time, Koolred or a partner may sponsor a promotion or contest or survey on the Website. You may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address, home address and to answer questions in order to participate.

We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to received information from.

It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

Your first name or display name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload any content including images or videos or send messages through Koolred. Other Users can contact you through your message box in Koolred or leave comments.

Any content including images or videos that you submit to the Koolred Services may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

## Information Sharing (Disclosure of Your Personal Information)

We do not share your personal identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other third party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

We may however provide relevant information to our partners, as discussed in this policy. We may aggregate personal information from all of our Users and provide that information in the aggregate to other parties, including advertisers, for marketing and promotional purposes. However, if we do so, that information will not be in a form that will allow any third party to identify you personally.

We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information to our parent company, subsidiaries and affiliated companies, or other business partners for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. 

Sharing such information allows us and our partners to better understand the ways in which our various product and service offerings can assist you.

We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We do share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, etc) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions and/or functionality on the Koolred Sites and Koolred Services.

We may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about Koolred, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links).

In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities.

Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Koolred specified purposes.

From time to time, we may be required to disclose your information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Koolred Service or using the Koolred name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

## Invitations and Other Communications to Non-Members

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We will automatically send an email inviting your friend to join the site.

Koolred stores this email address for the purpose of automatically adding the respondent to the friends list of the Member sending this invitation, and also to send reminders of the invitation.

Recipients of invitations from Koolred may contact Koolred to request the removal of their information from our database.

Koolred Members may also store email addresses of people they know in their internal Koolred address book and may also choose to send invitations and other communications to those addresses.

## Use of Cookies

Koolred uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is an industry practice, and most websites use them to provide useful features for their customers. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. Cookies cannot be used to read data off of your hard drive, and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other websites.

You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Koolred Services may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. We encourage you accept cookies to enjoy full use of the website. We use cookies in this manner to help us understand how visitors use our site, and to help us to improve our site. It is also to ensure that you are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and web page content based on browser type and user profile information.

## Links

Koolred may contain links to other websites or links placed by other Users. We will caution you to read the privacy statements of such websites when you visit them. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. 

Our Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected on Koolred Website.

## Broadcast to Third-Party Services and Location Information

You can opt-in to broadcast your Koolred activity to third-party sites (e.g. Facebook and Twitter). You have full control of which activities you perform on Koolred, will be broadcasted on such third-party sites. In the event you opt-in to this service, you acknowledge that such information so broadcasted no longer falls under the control of Koolred and is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of such third-party sites. Consequently, Koolred shall not be made responsible for any privacy infringement resulting thereto.

Your location information can be publicly displayed to other Users and on third-party sites in accordance with your privacy and opt-in settings. In the event you opt-in to this service, you acknowledge that privacy of such information will be beyond the control of Koolred and is subjected to the terms of use and privacy policies of such third-party sites. Please take note that your location information which you share may be forwarded to others without your knowledge and hence, you should only share your location with people you know and trust. Consequently, Koolred shall not be made responsible for any privacy infringement resulting thereto. 

## Chat Room, Weblogs (Blogs), Message Boards, Public Forums

Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (

in messages, chat areas, on forums within your public profile page, etc) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others to send you unsolicited emails.

In this manner, Koolred will not be responsible over the security of your personal information. 

## Correcting/Updating or Removing Information (How You Can Review and Update Your Personal Information)

You may modify or remove any of your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info. Information will be updated immediately.

You may deactivate your account and may do so on the Account Settings page.

Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of Koolred.

## Email Choice/Opt-out (Your Choices)

If you no longer wish to receive our email updates or other email notifications, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by changing your settings in the "Account Settings" section of the website. You can access this page by clicking on the "Me" and to "My Profile" link on the top of your Koolred homepage. All Koolred newsletters and notification emails will include the above instructions for opting-out of future communications.

## Special Note to International Users

All Koolred Services, including the protection of personal information collected via the Koolred Services, are governed by the laws of Malaysia, this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, and where practicable, we endeavour to adopt internet best practices. If you are a User accessing the Koolred Services from outside of Malaysia or any country with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from Malaysian laws, your continued use of the Koolred Services shall signify your consent to having your personal information transferred to and/or stored in Malaysia.

## Change of Ownership (In the Event of Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy)

In the event of a change of ownership, or a direct merger with or acquisition by another entity, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the Koolred Service can continue operating in your best interest. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

## Security (Steps We Take to Protect Your Personal Information/Our Commitment to Data Security)

All members' accounts are protected by member-created-passwords.

We take every precaution to protect the member information, as well as information collected from other Users of the Website. We use reasonable measures to protect your personal information that is stored on our servers and within our database andemploy processes such as password hashing, login auditing, and idle session termination to protect against unauthorized access to your personal information.

Access to your information is limited to employees needing to perform their job functions, such as customer service personnel and technical staff.

However, please note that we cannot guarantee that member information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of your personal information at any time. If we learn of a systems security breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. We may post a notice on the Site if a security breach occurs.

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy

Koolred reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this Policy at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted on the Website and you are encouraged to check the Website from time to time for updates and change. You have the right to maintain or remove any or part of your details that are affected by these revisions. Your continued use of Koolred will signify your agreement to such changes. 

## Questions or Comments

Users with questions about this Privacy Policy and any of the abovementioned statements may contact Koolred at [askus@koolred.com](mailto:askus@Koolred.com)

**USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY**

Updated: 25 January 2011
